AITOR MOYA MUÑOZ

Flat 2, 233 Chesterton Road, Cambridge CB4 1AS 07445037244 blomo.official@gmail.com LinkedIn and Other Links

Career Objective

A hard worker sound engineer with more than ten years of experience handling all kind of instruments and music equipment, interactions in different environments. I am looking to apply for the role of Sound Designer.

My aim is to create audio of the best possible quality, so keep improving my abilities in a top-level environment. Due to my passion and dedication to audio I value working on finding the desired sounds to match the energy of a project. I feel comfortable facing challenges, I am a fast learner with advanced knowledge of sound design, studio techniques and audio implementation software like Wwise.

Work Experience

July 2016 – Present: Self-employed, Blomo Music Producer / Sound Designer

Produce music of many genres and styles. I create my own digital sounds as well as audio sample libraries by playing and recording foley or acoustic instruments.

My compositions include music and sound design two videogames, dancing performances, short films, animation short movies and live firework shows. I also did Contemporary, Classical pieces, soundtracks, and music as EDM, Jazz, Hip Hop, Rock, Fusion and Pop.

July 2016 – Present: Self-employed, Blomo Mixing and mastering engineer

I was responsible of the final quality and results of Blomo Productions music. I used to work with all kind of tools for mixing and mastering, adapting myself to hardware like the Audient ASP 8024 Mixer, and software from Waves, Plugin Alliance or iZotope. Control of the technical aspects, my ears audacity, professional point of view in the creative and technical process.

Sept. 2014 – Sept. 2016: Diables de l'OnyarMy role was to play my songs of 30 to 45 minutes over a fireworks live show. I played a live setup following the firework patterns and coordinating my music with different scenes. Before the shows I had to setup the audio and lights on the stage with the other members of the company.

Apr. 2011 – Sept. 2014: Diables de l'Onyar
Being a director of a drumband required knowing all the rhythms of all the instruments and

creating choreographies, as well as meeting the individuals needs of the other musicians. As a composer, I had to be aware of the skills differences, adapting the songs to all the group members as well as maintaining the essence of the show.

Education & Qualification

September 2018 – present: Audio and Music Technology (BSc Hons) First

First-Class Honours

Anglia Ruskin University - Cambridge, UK.

Final project: Music Business for Social Purposes

The studies include: Music Production, Recording Techniques, Composition Software, Sound Design for Film and Videogames, Advanced Studio Practice, Entrepreneurship.

September 2011 - 2016: Mechanical Engineering

75% finished

Universitat de Girona - Girona, Spain.

More than the 75% of the credits finished. The studies include: Physics, Chemistry, Mechanics, Electronics, Computer Science, Fluid Mechanics, Statistics, Business.

AITOR MOYA MUÑOZ

Skills

Computing/IT

Professional level: DAWS (Ableton Live, Logic Pro, ProTools)

High level: Sound Implementation (WWise), Main OS (macOS, Windows), Basic software (Office)

Intermediate level: Video Software (Adobe Premiere Pro, After Effects)

Website development (Shopify, WordPress, PageFly) and Code Writing (PureData, C++).

International / Multicultural music knowledge

I have knowledge of Latin, African, Asian and European music, which allows me to work comfortably in all kind of projects.

I play more than 15 instruments in a level that allow me to create samples with them. Adaptive, fast and easy understanding of what other artists wants to do and work with them empathically.

Social media / business and marketing

As a freelancer I use social networks to share my products, being aware of analytics, how to post to get the best audience possible and spread my image into the market. As well, I have a solid knowledge of the website development and design process.

Social media: Facebook, Youtube, Soundcloud, Bandcamp, Twitter, Instagram.

Creative abilities / Resourceful

My creative mindset allows me to build big schemes in a short amount of time, to work out of the box, to develop parallel thinking and find solutions to unexpected issues.

Adaptive and innovative in terms of resources, having my passion as the main strength source. I am ever looking to learn new procedures and tips on the studio, but I am also able to work following a strict methodology when it is required.

Additional Experience

Sound designer

Sound designer for the videogame 'Claim Showdown' (2021) and short films 'Gills and Fins' (2020) and 'Downfall' (2020) plus music composing, recording and producing.

Website designer

Designer and creator of the eCommerce website start-up 'BomGo'.

Music composer

Composer of three soundtracks of 30-45 minutes for Diables de l'Onyar fireworks show. Composer and producer of the music for the Performing Arts final project <u>'A War Without Smoke'</u>.

Achievements and Interests

Some of my greatest experiences within the music have been to tour with a drumband around Europe, working as an invited artist on big events like the <u>Acampada Jove festival</u>, as well as playing music on more than five European countries earning an average salary with it. My last achievement has been the creation of the social enterprise BomGo with all its content, as well as learning about website design, business, marketing, and creating relationships with a national-wide company to promote the company and a social project.